"Alfa Romeos","ORGANIZATION"
"GM","ORGANIZATION"
"Fiat","ORGANIZATION"
"six-cylinder petrol engines","QUANTITY"
"Alfa Romeo","ORGANIZATION"
"Italian","OTHER"
"Fiat","ORGANIZATION"
"Fiat","LOCATION"
"Arese","LOCATION"
"Milan","LOCATION"
"six-cylinder engines","QUANTITY"
"General Motors","ORGANIZATION"
"Fiat","ORGANIZATION"
"GM","ORGANIZATION"
"Australia","LOCATION"
"GM","ORGANIZATION"
"Fiat","ORGANIZATION"
"GM","ORGANIZATION"
"Fiat","ORGANIZATION"
"1.55bn euros","QUANTITY"
"$2bn","QUANTITY"
"£1.1bn","QUANTITY"
"Italian","OTHER"
"Fiat","ORGANIZATION"
"GM","ORGANIZATION"
"five-year","QUANTITY"
"two joint ventures","QUANTITY"
"Powertrain","ORGANIZATION"
"today","DATE"
"Alfa Romeo","ORGANIZATION"
"Arese","ORGANIZATION"
"Vincenzo Lilliu","PERSON"
"Reuters","ORGANIZATION"
"six-cylinder","QUANTITY"
"Alfa Romeo","ORGANIZATION"
"GM","ORGANIZATION"
"Australia","ORGANIZATION"
"Reuters","ORGANIZATION"
"Lilliu","PERSON"
"Fiat","ORGANIZATION"
"Luca di Montezemolo","PERSON"
"Tuesday","DATE"
"Arese","LOCATION"
"800 jobs","QUANTITY"
"Alfa Romeo","ORGANIZATION"
"six-cylinder","QUANTITY"
"147 156 156 Sportwagon 166 GTV GT and Spider","COMMERCIAL_ITEM"
